<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="main_accessibility_help_button">Help</string>
    <string name="main_help_description">
        S\&amp;P500 index is loaded. It contains 505 issuers, but Finnhub discourages to make more
        than 30 network requests per second, so the list\nis chunked on up to 2 chunks are fetched
        at a time. If you need more issuers, pull to refresh list to request more. New-York Stock
        \nMarket is open from 16:30 to 2:00 Moscow time (GMT+3). Thus, real-time updates may not be
        \navailable out this period. First load is normally slow, be patient :).
        \n
        \nLicense: Alov Maxim alovmax@yandex.ru. All right reserved.
        This software belongs only to it\'s author.
        \nNon-commercial use disclaimer:
        \n
        \nThis Work has been digitized in a public-private partnership. As part of this partnership,
        \nthe partners have agreed to limit commercial uses of this digital representation of the
        \nWork by third parties. You can, without permission, copy, modify, distribute, display, or
        \nperform the Item, for non-commercial uses. For any other permissible uses, please review
        \nthe terms and conditions of the organization that has made the Item available.
        \n
        \nUnless expressly stated otherwise, the organization that has made this Item available makes
        \nno warranties about the Item and cannot guarantee the accuracy of this Rights Statement.
        \nYou are responsible for your own use.
        \n
        \nYou may find additional information about the copyright status of the Item on the website
        \nof the organization that has made the Item available.
        \n
        \nYou may need to obtain other permissions for your intended use. For example, other rights
        \nsuch as publicity, privacy, or moral rights may limit how you may use the material.
    </string>
    <string name="main_help_title">Help</string>
    <string name="main_stock_request_error">Failed to get stocks\nPlease try again</string>
    <string name="main_stock_request_error_button">Retry</string>
    <string name="main_search_popular_requests_title">Popular requests</string>
    <string name="main_search_recent_results_title">You\&apos;ve searched for this</string>
    <string name="main_search_suggestions_title">Stocks</string>
    <string name="main_tab_favourite">Favourite</string>
    <string name="main_tab_stocks">Stocks</string>
</resources>
